[
  {
    "id": "202",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company needs to share an Amazon S3 bucket with an external vendor. The bucket owner must be able to access all objects. Which action should be taken to share the S3 bucket? ",
      "answers": [
        "Update the bucket to be a Requester Pays bucket.",
        "Update the bucket to enable cross-origin resource sharing (CORS).",
        "Create a bucket policy to require users to grant bucket-owner-full-control when uploading objects.",
        "Create an IAM policy to require users to grant bucket-owner-full-control when uploading objects."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a bucket policy to require users to grant bucket-owner-full-control when uploading objects."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "203",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is developing a real-time multiplier game that uses UDP for communications between client and servers in an Auto Scaling group. Spikes in demand are anticipated during the day, so the game server platform must adapt accordingly. Developers want to store gamer scores and other non-relational data in a database solution that will scale without intervention. Which solution should a solution architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Route 53 for traffic distribution and Amazon Aurora Serverless for data storage.",
        "Use a Network Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon DynamoDB on demand for data storage.",
        "Use a Network Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon Aura Global for data storage.",
        "Use an Application Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon DynamoDB global tables for data storage."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a Network Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon DynamoDB on demand for data storage."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "204",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company collects temperature, humidity, and atmospheric pressure data in cities across multiple continents. The average volume of data collected per site each day is 500 GB. Each site has a high-speed internet connection. The companys weather forecasting applications are based in a single Region and analyze the data daily. What is the FASTEST way to aggregate data for all of these global sites?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration on the destination bucket. Use multipart uploads to directly upload site data to the destination bucket.",
        "Upload site data to an Amazon S3 bucket in the closest AWS Region. Use S3 cross-Region replication to copy objects to the destination bucket.",
        "Schedule AWS Snowball jobs daily to transfer data to the closest AWS Region. Use S3 cross-Region replication to copy objects to the destination bucket.",
        "Upload the data to an Amazon EC2 instance in the closes Region. Store the data in an Amazon EBS volume. One a day take an EBS snapshot and copy it to the centralize Region. Restore the EBS volume in the centralized Region and run an analysis on the data daily."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration on the destination bucket. Use multipart uploads to directly upload site data to the destination bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "205",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a custom application running on an Amazon EC instance that: 1)Reads a large amount of data from Amazon S3  2)Performs a multi-stage analysis  3)Writes the results to Amazon DynamoDB. The application writes a significant number of large temporary files during the multi-stage analysis. The process performance depends on the temporary storage performance. What would be the fastest storage option for holding the temporary files?",
      "answers": [
        "Multiple Amazon S3 buckets with Transfer Acceleration for storage.",
        "Multiple Amazon EBS drives with Provisioned IOPS and EBS optimization.",
        "Multiple Amazon EFS volumes using the Network I lie System version 4.1 (NFSv4.1) protocol.",
        "Multiple instance store volumes with software RAID 0."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Multiple instance store volumes with software RAID 0."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "206",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A leasing company generates and emails PDF statements every month for all its customers. Each statement is about 400 KB in size. Customers can download their statements from the website for up to 30 days from when the statements were generated. At the end of their 3-year lease, the customers are emailed a ZIP file that contains all the statements. What is the MOST cost-effective storage solution for this situation?",
      "answers": [
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier storage after 1 day.",
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Glacier storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive storage after 30 days.",
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA) storage after 30 days.",
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA) storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier storage after 30 days."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA) storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier storage after 30 days."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "207",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently released a new type of internet-connected sensor. The company is expecting to sell thousands of sensors, which are designed to stream high volumes of data each second to a central location. A solutions architect must design a solution that ingests and stores data so that engineering teams can analyze it in near-real time with millisecond responsiveness. Which solution should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an Amazon SQS queue to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon Redshift.",
        "Use an Amazon SOS queue to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon DynamoDB.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon Redshift.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon DynamoDB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon DynamoDB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "208",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A website runs a web application that receives a burst of traffic each day at noon. The users upload new pictures and content daily, but have been complaining of timeouts. The architecture uses Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups, and the custom application consistently takes 1 minute to initiate upon boot up before responding to user requests. How should a solutions architect redesign the architecture to better respond to changing traffic?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer with a slow start configuration.",
        "Configure AWS ElastiCache for Redis to offload direct requests to the servers.",
        "Configure an Auto Scaling step scaling policy with an instance warmup condition.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront to use an Application Load Balancer as the origin."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Auto Scaling step scaling policy with an instance warmup condition."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "209",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is concerned that two NAT instances in use will no longer be able to support the traffic needed for the companys application. A solutions architect wants to implement a solution that is highly available fault tolerant, and automatically scalable. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Remove the two NAT instances and replace them with two NAT gateways in the same Availability Zone.",
        "Use Auto Scaling groups with Network Load Balancers for the NAT instances in different Availability Zones.",
        "Remove the two NAT instances and replace them with two NAT gateways in different Availability Zones.",
        "Replace the two NAT instances with Spot Instances in different Availability Zones and deploy a Network Load Balancer."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Remove the two NAT instances and replace them with two NAT gateways in different Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "210",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company operates a website on Amazon EC2 Linux instances. Some of the instances are failing. Troubleshooting points to insufficient swap space on the failed instances. The operations team lead needs a solution to monitor this. What should a solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch Swap Usage metric dimension. Monitor the Swap Usage dimension in the EC2 metrics in CloudWatch.",
        "Use EC2 metadata to collect information, then publish it to Amazon CloudWatch custom metrics. Monitor Swap Usage metrics in CloudWatch.",
        "Install an Amazon CloudWatch agent on the instances. Run an appropriate script on a set schedule. Monitor Swap Utilization metrics in CloudWatch.",
        "Enable detailed monitoring in the EC2 console. Create an Amazon CloudWatch Swap Utilization custom metric. Monitor Swap Utilization metrics in CloudWatch."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Install an Amazon CloudWatch agent on the instances. Run an appropriate script on a set schedule. Monitor Swap Utilization metrics in CloudWatch."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "211",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company has a web server running on an Amazon EC2 instance in a public subnet with an Elastic IP address. The default security group is assigned to the EC2 instance. The default network ACL has been modified to block all traffic. A solutions architect needs to make the web server accessible from everywhere on port 443. Which combination of steps will accomplish this task? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Create a security group with a rule to allow TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Create a security group with a rule to allow TCP port 443 to destination 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow inbound/outbound TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0 and to destination 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow inbound TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0 and outbound TCP port 32768-65535 to destination 0/0.0.0/0."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a security group with a rule to allow TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow inbound TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0 and outbound TCP port 32768-65535 to destination 0/0.0.0/0."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company must re-evaluate its need for the Amazon EC2 instances it currently has provisioned in an Auto Scaling group. At present, the Auto Scaling group is configured for a minimum of two instances and a maximum of four instances across two Availability Zones. A Solutions architect reviewed Amazon CloudWatch metrics and found that CPU utilization is consistently low for all the EC2 instances. What should the solutions architect recommend to maximize utilization while ensuring the application remains fault tolerant?",
      "answers": [
        "Remove some EC2 instances to increase the utilization of remaining instances.",
        "Increase the Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) capacity of instances with less CPU utilization.",
        "Modify the Auto Scaling group scaling policy to scale in and out based on a higher CPU utilization metric.",
        "Create a new launch configuration that uses smaller instance types. Update the existing Auto Scaling group."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a new launch configuration that uses smaller instance types. Update the existing Auto Scaling group."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "213",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an application that posts messages to Amazon SQS. Another application polls the queue and processes the messages in an I/O-intensive operation. The company has a service level agreement (SLA) that specifies the maximum amount of time that can elapse between receiving the messages and responding to the users. Due to an increase in the number of messages the company has difficulty meeting its SLA consistently. What should a solutions architect do to help improve the applications processing time and ensure it can handle the load at any level?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Terminate the instance and replace it with a larger size.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Terminate the instance and replace it with an Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instance.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Create an Auto Scaling group using this image in its launch configuration. Configure the group with a target tracking policy to keep us aggregate CPU utilization below 70%.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Create an Auto Scaling group using this image in its launch configuration. Configure the group with a target tracking policy based on the age of the oldest message in the SQS queue."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Create an Auto Scaling group using this image in its launch configuration. Configure the group with a target tracking policy based on the age of the oldest message in the SQS queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "214",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is designing a new service that will run on Amazon EC2 instance behind an Elastic Load Balancer. However, many of the web service clients can only reach IP addresses whitelisted on their firewalls. What should a solution architect recommend to meet the clients needs?",
      "answers": [
        "A Network Load Balancer with an associated Elastic IP address.",
        "An Application Load Balancer with an associated Elastic IP address",
        "An A record in an Amazon Route 53 hosted zone pointing to an Elastic IP address",
        "An EC2 instance with a public IP address running as a proxy in front of the load balancer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["A Network Load Balancer with an associated Elastic IP address."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "215",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to host a web application on AWS that will communicate to a database within a VPC. The application should be highly available. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Create two Amazon EC2 instances to host the web servers behind a load balancer, and then deploy the database on a large instance.",
        "Deploy a load balancer in multiple Availability Zones with an Auto Scaling group for the web servers, and then deploy Amazon RDS in multiple Availability Zones.",
        "Deploy a load balancer in the public subnet with an Auto Scaling group for the web servers, and then deploy the database on an Amazon EC2 instance in the private subnet.",
        "Deploy two web servers with an Auto Scaling group, configure a domain that points to the two web servers, and then deploy a database architecture in multiple Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy a load balancer in multiple Availability Zones with an Auto Scaling group for the web servers, and then deploy Amazon RDS in multiple Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "216",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys packaged application dynamically creates and returns single-use text files in response to user requests. The company is using Amazon CloudFront for distribution, but wants to future reduce data transfer costs. The company cannot modify the applications source code. What should a solution architect do to reduce costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Lambda@Edge to compress the files as they are sent to users.",
        "Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration to reduce the response times.",
        "Enable caching on the CloudFront distribution to store generated files at the edge.",
        "Use Amazon S3 multipart uploads to move the files to Amazon S3 before returning them to users."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Lambda@Edge to compress the files as they are sent to users."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "217",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A database is on an Amazon RDS MySQL 5.6 Multi-AZ DB instance that experience highly dynamic reads. Application developers notice a significant slowdown when testing read performance from a secondary AWS Region. The developers want a solution that provides less than 1 second of read replication latency. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Install MySQL on Amazon EC2 in the secondary Region.",
        "Migrate the database to Amazon Aurora with cross-Region replicas.",
        "Create another RDS for MySQL read replica in the secondary.",
        "Implement Amazon ElastiCache to improve database query performance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Migrate the database to Amazon Aurora with cross-Region replicas."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "218",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is planning to deploy an Amazon RDS DB instance running Amazon Aurora. The company has a backup retention policy requirement of 90 days. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Set the backup retention period to 90 days when creating the RDS DB instance.",
        "Configure RDS to copy automated snapshots to a user-managed Amazon S3 bucket with a lifecycle policy set to delete after 90 days.",
        "Create an AWS Backup plan to perform a daily snapshot of the RDS database with the retention set to 90 days. Create an AWS Backup job to schedule the execution of the backup plan daily.",
        "Use a daily scheduled event with Amazon CloudWatch Events to execute a custom AWS Lambda function that makes a copy of the RDS automated snapshot. Purge snapshots older than 90 days."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an AWS Backup plan to perform a daily snapshot of the RDS database with the retention set to 90 days. Create an AWS Backup job to schedule the execution of the backup plan daily."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "219",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company currently has 250 TB of backup files stored in Amazon S3 in a vendors proprietary format. Using a Linux-based software application provided by the vendor, the company wants to retrieve files from Amazon S3, transform the files to an industry-standard format, and re-upload them to Amazon S3. The company wants to minimize the data transfer charges associated with this conversation. What should a solution architect do to accomplish this? ",
      "answers": [
        "Install the conversion software as an Amazon S3 batch operation so the data is transformed without leaving Amazon S3.",
        "Install the conversion software onto an on-premises virtual machine. Perform the transformation and re-upload the files to Amazon S3 from the virtual machine.",
        "Use AWS Snowball Edge device to expert the data and install the conversion software onto the devices. Perform the data transformation and re-upload the files to Amazon S3 from the Snowball Edge devices.",
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in the same Region as Amazon S3 and install the conversion software onto the instance. Perform the transformation and re- upload the files to Amazon S3 from the EC2 instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in the same Region as Amazon S3 and install the conversion software onto the instance. Perform the transformation and re- upload the files to Amazon S3 from the EC2 instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "220",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is migrating a NoSQL database cluster to Amazon EC2. The database automatically replicates data to maintain at least three copies of the data. I/O throughput of the servers is the highest priority. Which instance type should a solutions architect recommend for the migration?",
      "answers": [
        "Storage optimized instances with instance store",
        "Burstable general purpose instances with an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume",
        "Memory optimized instances with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) optimization enabled",
        "Compute optimized instances with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) optimization enabled"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Storage optimized instances with instance store"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "221",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a large Microsoft SharePoint deployment running on-premises that requires Microsoft Windows shared file storage. The company wants to migrate this workload to the AWS Cloud and is considering various storage options. The storage solution must be highly available and integrated with Active Directory for access control. Which solution will satisfy these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure Amazon EFS storage and set the Active Directory domain for authentication.",
        "Create an SMB file share on an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway in two Availability Zones.",
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket and configure Microsoft Windows Server to mount it as a volume.",
        "Create an Amazon FSx for Windows File Server file system on AWS and set the Active Directory domain for authentication."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon FSx for Windows File Server file system on AWS and set the Active Directory domain for authentication."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "222",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a web application with sporadic usage patterns. There is heavy usage at the beginning of each month, moderate usage at the start of each week, and unpredictable usage during the week. The application consists of a web server and a MySQL database server running inside the data center. The company would like to move the application to the AWS Cloud, and needs to select a cost-effective database platform that will not require database modifications. Which solution will meet these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL",
        "MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora Serverless",
        "MySQL deployed on Amazon EC2 in an Auto Scaling group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora Serverless"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "223",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing the storage architecture for a new web application used for storing and viewing engineering drawings. All application components will be deployed on the AWS infrastructure. The application design must support caching to minimize the amount of time that users wait for the engineering drawings to load. The application must be able to store petabytes of data. Which combination of storage and caching should the solutions architect use?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3 with Amazon CloudFront",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier with Amazon ElastiCache",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes with Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Storage Gateway with Amazon ElastiCache"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3 with Amazon CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "224",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts its core network services, including directory services and DNS, in its on promises data center. The data center is connected to the AWS Cloud using AWS Direct Connect (DX). Additional AWS accounts are planned that will require quick, cost-effective, and consistent access to these network services. What should a solutions architect implement to meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a DX connection in each new account. Route the network traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Configure VPC endpoints in the DX VPC for all required services. Route the network traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Create a VPN connection between each new account and the DX VPC. Route the network traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Configure AWS Transit Gateway between the accounts. Assigns DX to the transit gateway and route network traffic to the on-premises servers."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure AWS Transit Gateway between the accounts. Assigns DX to the transit gateway and route network traffic to the on-premises servers."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "225",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A-company receives structured and semi-structured data from various sources once every day. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that leverages big data processing frameworks. The data should be accessible using SQL queries and business intelligence tools. What should the solutions architect recommend to build the MOST high-performing solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Glue to process data and Amazon S3 to store data.",
        "Use Amazon EMR to process data and Amazon Redshift to store data.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 to process data and Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) to store data.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics to process data and Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) to store data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon EMR to process data and Amazon Redshift to store data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "226",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is creating an application that will handle batch processing of large amounts of data. The input data will be held in Amazon S3 and the output data will be stored in a different S3 bucket. For processing, the application will transfer the data over the network between multiple Amazon EC2 instances. What should the solutions architect do to reduce the overall data transfer costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Place all the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group.",
        "Place all the EC2 instances in the same AWS Region.",
        "Place all the EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone.",
        "Place all the EC2 instances in private subnets in multiple Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Place all the EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "227",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company operates an ecommerce website on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in an Auto Scaling group. The site is experiencing performance issues related to a high request rate from illegitimate external systems with changing IP addresses. The security team is worried about potential DDoS attacks against the website. The company must block the illegitimate incoming requests in a way that has a minimal impact on legitimate users. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy Amazon Inspector and associate it with the ALB.",
        "Deploy AWS WAF, associate it with the ALB, and configure a rate-limiting rule.",
        "Deploy rules to the network ACLs associated with the ALB to block the incoming traffic.",
        "Deploy Amazon GuardDuty and enable rate-limiting protection when configuring GuardDuty."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy AWS WAF, associate it with the ALB, and configure a rate-limiting rule."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "228",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting an election reporting website on AWS for users around the world. The website uses Amazon EC2 instances for the web and application tiers in an Auto Scaling group with Application Load Balancers. The database tier uses an Amazon RDS for MySQL database. The website is updated with election results once an hour and has historically observed hundreds of users accessing the reports. The company is expecting a significant increase in demand because of upcoming elections in different countries. A solutions architect must improve the websites ability to handle additional demand while minimizing the need for additional EC2 instances. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch an Amazon ElastiCache cluster to cache common database queries.",
        "Launch an Amazon CloudFront web distribution to cache commonly requested website content.",
        "Enable disk-based caching on the EC2 instances to cache commonly requested website content.",
        "Deploy a reverse proxy into the design using an EC2 instance with caching enabled for commonly requested website content."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch an Amazon CloudFront web distribution to cache commonly requested website content."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "229",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is running a three-tier web application to process credit card payments. The front-end user interface consists of static webpages. The application tier can have long-running processes. The database tier uses MySQL. The application is currently running on a single, general purpose large Amazon EC2 instance. A solutions architect needs to decouple the services to make the web application highly available. Which solution would provide the HIGHEST availability?",
      "answers": [
        "Move static assets to Amazon CloudFront. Leave the application in EC2 in an Auto Scaling group. Move the database to Amazon RDS to deploy Multi-AZ.",
        "Move static assets and the application into a medium EC2 instance. Leave the database on the large instance. Place both instances in an Auto Scaling group.",
        "Move static assets to Amazon S3, Move the application to AWS Lambda with the concurrency limit set. Move the database to Amazon DynamoDB with on- demand enabled.",
        "Move static assets to Amazon S3. Move the application to Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) containers with Auto Scaling enabled, Move the database to Amazon RDS to deploy Multi-AZ."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Move static assets to Amazon S3. Move the application to Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) containers with Auto Scaling enabled, Move the database to Amazon RDS to deploy Multi-AZ."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "230",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a two-tier web application. The application consists of a public-facing web tier hosted on Amazon EC2 in public subnets. The database tier consists of Microsoft SQL Server running on Amazon EC2 in a private subnet. Security is a high priority for the company. How should security groups be configured in this situation? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Configure the security group for the web tier to allow inbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the web tier to allow outbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on port 1433 from the security group for the web tier.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow outbound traffic on ports 443 and 1433 to the security group for the web tier.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on ports 443 and 1433 from the security group for the web tier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure the security group for the web tier to allow inbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on port 1433 from the security group for the web tier."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "231",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is building a website that relies on reading and writing to an Amazon DynamoDB database. The traffic associated with the website predictably peaks during business hours on weekdays and declines overnight and during weekends. A solutions architect needs to design a cost-effective solution that can handle the load. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable DynamoDB Accelerator (DAX) to cache the data.",
        "Enable Multi-AZ replication for the DynamoDB database.",
        "Enable DynamoDB auto scaling when creating the tables.",
        "Enable DynamoDB On-Demand capacity allocation when creating the tables."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable DynamoDB auto scaling when creating the tables."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "232",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Redshift for its data warehouse. The company wants to ensure high durability for its data in case of any component failure. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable concurrency scaling.",
        "Enable cross-Region snapshots.",
        "Increase the data retention period.",
        "Deploy Amazon Redshift in Multi-AZ."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable cross-Region snapshots."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "233",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has data stored in an on-premises data center that is used by several on-premises applications. The company wants to maintain its existing application environment and be able to use AWS services for data analytics and future visualizations. Which storage service should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "AWS Storage Gateway for files",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Storage Gateway for files"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "234",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect must design a solution that uses Amazon CloudFront with an Amazon S3 origin to store a static website. The companys security policy requires that all website traffic be inspected by AWS WAF. How should the solutions architect comply with these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an S3 bucket policy to accept requests coming from the AWS WAF Amazon Resource Name (ARN) only.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront to forward all incoming requests to AWS WAF before requesting content from the S3 origin.",
        "Configure a security group that allows Amazon CloudFront IP addresses to access Amazon S3 only. Associate AWS WAF to CloudFront.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3 to use an origin access identity (OAI) to restrict access to the S3 bucket. Enable AWS WAF on the distribution."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3 to use an origin access identity (OAI) to restrict access to the S3 bucket. Enable AWS WAF on the distribution."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "235",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a 143 TB MySQL database that it wants to migrate to AWS. The plan is to use Amazon Aurora MySQL as the platform going forward. The company has a 100 Mbps AWS Direct Connect connection to Amazon VPC. Which solution meets the companys needs and takes the LEAST amount of time?",
      "answers": [
        "Use a gateway endpoint for Amazon S3. Migrate the data to Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora.",
        "Upgrade the Direct Connect link to 500 Mbps. Copy the data to Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora.",
        "Order an AWS Snowmobile and copy the database backup to it. Have AWS import the data into Amazon S3. Import the backup into Aurora.",
        "Order four 50-TB AWS Snowball devices and copy the database backup onto them. Have AWS import the data into Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Order four 50-TB AWS Snowball devices and copy the database backup onto them. Have AWS import the data into Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "236",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts an online shopping application that stores all orders in an Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL Single-AZ DB instance. Management wants to eliminate single points of failure and has asked a solutions architect to recommend an approach to minimize database downtime without requiring any changes to the application code. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Convert the existing database instance to a Multi-AZ deployment by modifying the database instance and specifying the Multi-AZ option.",
        "Create a new RDS Multi-AZ deployment. Take a snapshot of the current RDS instance and restore the new Multi-AZ deployment with the snapshot.",
        "Create a read-only replica of the PostgreSQL database in another Availability Zone. Use Amazon Route 53 weighted record sets to distribute requests across the databases.",
        "Place the RDS for PostgreSQL database in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group with a minimum group size of two. Use Amazon Route 53 weighted record sets to distribute requests across instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Convert the existing database instance to a Multi-AZ deployment by modifying the database instance and specifying the Multi-AZ option."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "237",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection from its on-premises servers to AWS. The workloads using the connection are critical. The company requires a disaster recovery strategy with maximum resiliency that maintains the current connection bandwidth at a minimum. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up a new Direct Connect connection in another AWS Region.",
        "Set up a new AWS managed VPN connection in another AWS Region.",
        "Set up two new Direct Connect connections: one in the current AWS Region and one in another Region.",
        "Set up two new AWS managed VPN connections: one in the current AWS Region and one in another Region."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up two new Direct Connect connections: one in the current AWS Region and one in another Region."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "238",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a VPC with public and private subnets. The VPC and subnets use IPv4 CIDR blocks. There is one public subnet and one private subnet in each of three Availability Zones (AZs) for high availability. An internet gateway is used to provide internet access for the public subnets. The private subnets require access to the internet to allow Amazon EC2 instances to download software updates. What should the solutions architect do to enable internet access for the private subnets?",
      "answers": [
        "Create three NAT gateways, one for each public subnet in each AZ. Create a private route table for each AZ that forwards non-VPC traffic to the NAT gateway in its AZ.",
        "Create three NAT instances, one for each private subnet in each AZ. Create a private route table for each AZ that forwards non-VPC traffic to the NAT instance in its AZ.",
        "Create a second internet gateway on one of the private subnets. Update the route table for the private subnets that forward non-VPC traffic to the private internet gateway.",
        "Create an egress-only internet gateway on one of the public subnets. Update the route table for the private subnets that forward non-VPC traffic to the egress- only internet gateway."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create three NAT gateways, one for each public subnet in each AZ. Create a private route table for each AZ that forwards non-VPC traffic to the NAT gateway in its AZ."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "239",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "As part of budget planning, management wants a report of AWS billed items listed by user. The data will be used to create department budgets. A solutions architect needs to determine the most efficient way to obtain this report information. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Run a query with Amazon Athena to generate the report.",
        "Create a report in Cost Explorer and download the report.",
        "Access the bill details from the billing dashboard and download the bill.",
        "Modify a cost budget in AWS Budgets to alert with Amazon Simple Email Service (Amazon SES)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a report in Cost Explorer and download the report."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "240",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company with facilities in North America, Europe, and Asia is designing new distributed application to optimize its global supply chain and manufacturing process. The orders booked on one continent should be visible to all Regions in a second or less. The database should be able to support failover with a short Recovery Time Objective (RTO). The uptime of the application is important to ensure that manufacturing is not impacted. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon DynamoDB global tables.",
        "Use Amazon Aurora Global Database.",
        "Use Amazon RDS for MySQL with a cross-Region read replica.",
        "Use Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL with a cross-Region read replica."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Aurora Global Database."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "241",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A companys near-real-time streaming application is running on AWS. As the data is ingested, a job runs on the data and takes 30 minutes to complete. The workload frequently experiences high latency due to large amounts of incoming data. A solutions architect needs to design a scalable and serverless solution to enhance performance. Which combination of steps should the solutions architect take? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to ingest the data.",
        "Use AWS Lambda with AWS Step Functions to process the data.",
        "Use AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS) to ingest the data.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group to process the data.",
        "Use AWS Fargate with Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) to process the data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to ingest the data.",
        "Use AWS Fargate with Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) to process the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "242",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on an Amazon EC2 instance needs to access an Amazon DynamoDB table. Both the EC2 instance and the DynamoDB table are in the same AWS account. A solutions architect must configure the necessary permissions. Which solution will allow least privilege access to the DynamoDB table from the EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an IAM role with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Create an instance profile to assign this IAM role to the EC2 instance.",
        "Create an IAM role with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Add the EC2 instance to the trust relationship policy document to allow it to assume the role.",
        "Create an IAM user with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Store the credentials in an Amazon S3 bucket and read them from within the application code directly.",
        "Create an IAM user with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Ensure that the application stores the IAM credentials securely on local storage and uses them to make the DynamoDB calls."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an IAM role with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Create an instance profile to assign this IAM role to the EC2 instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "243",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a solution that involves orchestrating a series of Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) task types running on Amazon EC2 instances that are part of an ECS cluster. The output and state data for all tasks needs to be stored. The amount of data output by each task is approximately 10 MB, and there could be hundreds of tasks running at a time. The system should be optimized for high-frequency reading and writing. As old outputs are archived and deleted, the storage size is not expected to exceed 1 TB. Which storage solution should the solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "An Amazon DynamoDB table accessible by all ECS cluster instances.",
        "An Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with Provisioned Throughput mode.",
        "An Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) file system with Bursting Throughput mode.",
        "An Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume mounted to the ECS cluster instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["An Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with Provisioned Throughput mode."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "244",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An online photo application lets users upload photos and perform image editing operations. The application offers two classes of service: free and paid. Photos submitted by paid users are processed before those submitted by free users. Photos are uploaded to Amazon S3 and the job information is sent to Amazon SQS. Which configuration should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use one SQS FIFO queue. Assign a higher priority to the paid photos so they are processed first.",
        "Use two SQS FIFO queues: one for paid and one for free. Set the free queue to use short polling and the paid queue to use long polling.",
        "Use two SQS standard queues: one for paid and one for free. Configure Amazon EC2 instances to prioritize polling for the paid queue over the free queue.",
        "Use one SQS standard queue. Set the visibility timeout of the paid photos to zero. Configure Amazon EC2 instances to prioritize visibility settings so paid photos are processed first."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use two SQS standard queues: one for paid and one for free. Configure Amazon EC2 instances to prioritize polling for the paid queue over the free queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "245",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its MySQL database from on premises to AWS. The company recently experienced a database outage that significantly impacted the business. To ensure this does not happen again, the company wants a reliable database solution on AWS that minimizes data loss and stores every transaction on at least two nodes. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon RDS DB instance with synchronous replication to three nodes in three Availability Zones.",
        "Create an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance with Multi-AZ functionality enabled to synchronously replicate the data.",
        "Create an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance and then create a read replica in a separate AWS Region that synchronously replicates the data.",
        "Create an Amazon EC2 instance with a MySQL engine installed that triggers an AWS Lambda function to synchronously replicate the data to an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance with Multi-AZ functionality enabled to synchronously replicate the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "246",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company stores user data in AWS. The data is used continuously with peak usage during business hours. Access patterns vary, with some data not being used for months at a time. A solutions architect must choose a cost-effective solution that maintains the highest level of durability while maintaining high availability. Which storage solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3 Standard",
        "Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive",
        "Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "247",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company receives inconsistent service from its data center provider because the company is headquartered in an area affected by natural disasters. The company is not ready to fully migrate to the AWS Cloud, but it wants a failure environment on AWS in case the on-premises data center fails. The company runs web servers that connect to external vendors. The data available on AWS and on premises must be uniform. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend that has the LEAST amount of downtime?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Run application servers on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Execute an AWS CloudFormation template from a script to create Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection between a VPC and the data center. Run application servers on Amazon EC2 in an Auto Scaling group. Run an AWS Lambda function to execute an AWS CloudFormation template to create an Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Run an AWS Lambda function to execute an AWS CloudFormation template to launch two Amazon EC2 instances. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3. Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection between a VPC and the data center."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Run application servers on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "248",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has three VPCs named Development, Testing, and Production in the us-east-1 Region. The three VPCs need to be connected to an on-premises data center and are designed to be separate to maintain security and prevent any resource sharing. A solutions architect needs to find a scalable and secure solution. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an AWS Direct Connect connection and a VPN connection for each VPC to connect back to the data center.",
        "Create VPC peers from all the VPCs to the Production VPC. Use an AWS Direct Connect connection from the Production VPC back to the data center.",
        "Connect VPN connections from all the VPCs to a VPN in the Production VPC. Use a VPN connection from the Production VPC back to the data center.",
        "Create a new VPC called Network. Within the Network VPC, create an AWS Transit Gateway with an AWS Direct Connect connection back to the data center. Attach all the other VPCs to the Network VPC."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a new VPC called Network. Within the Network VPC, create an AWS Transit Gateway with an AWS Direct Connect connection back to the data center. Attach all the other VPCs to the Network VPC."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "249",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What should a solutions architect do to ensure that all objects uploaded to an Amazon S3 bucket are encrypted? ",
      "answers": [
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an s3:x-amz-acl header set.",
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an s3:x-amz-acl header set to private.",
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an aws:SecureTransport header set to true.",
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an x-amz-server-side-encryption header set."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an x-amz-server-side-encryption header set."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "250",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company needs a secure connection between its on-premises environment and AWS. This connection does not need high bandwidth and will handle a small amount of traffic. The connection should be set up quickly. What is the MOST cost-effective method to establish this type of connection? ",
      "answers": [
        "Implement a client VPN.",
        "Implement AWS Direct Connect.",
        "Implement a bastion host on Amazon EC2.",
        "Implement an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "251",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses Application Load Balancers (ALBs) in different AWS Regions. The ALBs receive inconsistent traffic that can spike and drop throughout the year. The companys networking team needs to allow the IP addresses of the ALBs in the on-premises firewall to enable connectivity. Which solution is the MOST scalable with minimal configuration changes?",
      "answers": [
        "Write an AWS Lambda script to get the IP addresses of the ALBs in different Regions. Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow the IP addresses of the ALBs.",
        "Migrate all ALBs in different Regions to the Network Load Balancer (NLBs). Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow the Elastic IP addresses of all the NLBs.",
        "Launch AWS Global Accelerator. Register the ALBs in different Regions to the accelerator. Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow static IP addresses associated with the accelerator.",
        "Launch a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in one Region. Register the private IP addresses of the ALBs in different Regions with the NLB. Update the on- premises firewalls rule to allow the Elastic IP address attached to the NLB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch AWS Global Accelerator. Register the ALBs in different Regions to the accelerator. Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow static IP addresses associated with the accelerator."]
    }
  }
]